# Adrian Vincent T. Tayag

Marikina City, NCR • adrvntyg@gmail.com • +639277790469 linkedin.com/in/adriantayag

# **Background**

Results-oriented fresh graduate with experience in designing and manufacturing electronics modules in small quantities. Has background in circuit analysis, design and manufacturing, embedded systems, programming, and management dynamics. Exhibits motivation and perseverance in obtaining knowledge through experience.



### **Education**

University of the Philippines Los Baňos BS Electrical Engineering, Major in Electronics August 2014 - December 2019

# **Experience**

Sirkito LB March 2019 – Present

### **Co-Owner**

Sirkito LB is a local electronics retailer that caters to the project and hobby needs of Electrical Engineering students in UPLB

- Designed and manufactured in-house modules to cater the specific needs of fellow electrical engineering students
- Led and strategized the campaign to achieve ROI within the first 3 months of operation

## VR Philippines

August 2015 – Present

#### **Core Team Member**

VR Philippines is a tech community composed of VR enthusiasts and developers that aims to expose and advocate Virtual Reality technology in the Philippines

- Organized several events which further introduced more people to the Virtual Reality technology
- Facilitated coding workshops for VR game development in events organized by Google, PHINMA University of Pangasinan and others

#### **VISIV UPLB**

August 2017 – August 2019

## **Founding President**

VISIV UPLB is student organization that advocates the exploration of emerging technologies and creation of a hub for homegrown student projects in UPLB

- Led the organization in conducting intraorganizational workshops and seminars to upskill members in the organization's topics of interests
- Accomplished recruitment of 30+ members, facilitation of 5+ upskilling workshops, organization of 2 major events, and collaboration with 3 partner organizations

# **Training and Certifications**

**Harvard University** 

May 2020

### **CS50x - Introduction to Computer Science**

- Topics Covered: C, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Flask
- Course Duration: 8 Weeks
- Certificate ID: 1051c4a2-d4f6-4324-9a53-6a10ce2c20fd

# Mechaniweb - Autodesk Authorized Academic Partner Fusion 360 Monthly Challenge 2019

• Topics Covered: Parametric Sketches, Constraints, Sheet Metal, Joints

• Course Duration: 16 Hours

• Certificate ID: AP702151096066564643976

### **Skills**

**Software:** AutoCad, Eagle, Fusion 360, LTSpice, MATLAB **Programming:** C, C#, C++, Node.js, SQL, Python, VHDL, Web development

Microcontrollers: Arduino, Raspberry Pi, STM32

**Laboratory Methods:** Circuit analysis via operation of oscilloscope, signal generator,

multimeter, and other related laboratory equipment.

Miscellaneous Skills: PCB etching and assembly, Urban Agriculture, Virtual Reality

### References

### **Cristopher David**

Founder, VR Philippines

Chief Technology Officer, Veer Immersive Technologies, Inc.

Email Address: toph@veerimmersive.tech

### Melvin C. Ilang-Ilang

Instructor 7, Department of Electrical Engineering, College of Engineering and Agro-Industrial Technology, UPLB

Email Address: mcilangilang3@up.edu.ph

#### **Paolo Rommel Sanchez**

Assistant Professor 7, Agricultural Machinery Division, Institute of Agricultural Engineering, College of Engineering and Agro-Industrial Technology, UPLB

Email Address: ppsanchez@up.edu.ph